<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Indian route</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second_">Second_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main21">Main2Activity1</string>

    <string-array name="filler">
        <item name="Ahmedabad">It wins you over with its wealth of architecture.</item>
        <item name="Kolkata">India\’s second-biggest city is a daily festival of human existence.</item>
        <item name="Delhi">This pulsating metropolis has a bigger population than Australia.</item>
        <item name="Hyderabad">The city of smiles, of lights, of a thousand faces, called the Pearl City.</item>
        <item name="Lucknow">This bustling city is famed for its Nawabi era finesse and amazing food.</item>
        <item name="Chennai">Among Chennai\’s greatest assets are its people, infectiously enthusiastic about their hometown.</item>
        <item name="Bangalore">The IT hub of India, Dubbed India\'s Silicon Valley.</item>
        <item name="Mumbai">Mumbai is India\’s financial powerhouse and fashion epicentre.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="city">

        <item name="Ahmedabad">Ahmedabad</item>
        <item name="Kolkata">Kolkata</item>
        <item name="Delhi">Delhi</item>
        <item name="Hyderabad">Hyderabad</item>
        <item name="Lucknow">Lucknow</item>
        <item name="Chennai">Chennai</item>
        <item name="Bangalore">Bangalore</item>
        <item name="Mumbai">Mumbai</item>
    </string-array>
        <string-array name="desc">
            <item name="ahmedabad">Ahmedabad is the largest city and former capital of Gujarat, which is a state in India. It is the administrative headquarters of the Ahmedabad district and the seat of the Gujarat High Court. With a population of more than 6.3 million and an extended population of 7.8 million, it is the sixth largest city and seventh largest metropolitan area of India. Ahmedabad is located on the banks of the Sabarmati River, 30 km (19 mi) from the state capital Gandhinagar, which is its twin city.Ahmedabad has emerged as an important economic and industrial hub in India. It is the second largest producer of cotton in India, and its stock exchange is the country\'s second oldest. Cricket is a popular sport in Ahmedabad, which houses the 54,000-seat Sardar Patel Stadium. The effects of liberalisation of the Indian economy have energised the city\'s economy towards tertiary sector activities such as commerce, communication and construction. Ahmedabad\'s increasing population has resulted in an increase in the construction and housing industries resulting in recent development of skyscrapers.</item>
            <item name="Kolkata">Kolkata is the capital of the Indian state of West Bengal. Located on the east bank of the Hooghly River, it is the principal commercial, cultural, and educational centre of East India,while the Port of Kolkata is India\'s oldest operating port and its sole major riverine port. In 2011, the city had a population of 4.5 million, while the population of the city and its suburbs was 14.1 million, making it the third-most populous metropolitan area in India. Recent estimates of Kolkata Metropolitan Area\'s economy have ranged from $60 to $150 billion (GDP adjusted for purchasing power parity) making it third most-productive metropolitan area in India, after Mumbai and Delhi.</item>
            <item name="Delhi">Delhi officially the National Capital Territory of Delhi or NCT, is a city and a union territory of India. It is bordered by Haryana on three sides and by Uttar Pradesh to the east. The NCT covers an area of 1,484 square kilometres(573 sq mi). According to 2011 census, Delhi\'s city population was about 11 million, the second highest in India after Mumbai, while the whole NCT population was about 16.8 million. Delhi\'s urban area is now considered to extend beyond the NCT boundary to include an estimated population of over 26 million people making it the world\'s second largest urban area. As of 2016 recent estimates" of the metro economy of its urban area have ranked Delhi either the top or second most productive metro area of India. Delhi is the second wealthiest city after Mumbai in India, with a total wealth of $450 billion and home to 18 billionaires and 23,000 millionaires.</item>
            <item name="Hyderabad">Hyderabad is the capital of the southern Indian state of Telangana and de jure capital of Andhra Pradesh. Occupying 650 square kilometres (250 sq mi) along the banks ofthe Musi River, it has a population of about 6.7 million and a metropolitan population of about 7.75 million, making it the fourth most populous city and sixth most populous urban agglomeration in India. At an average altitude of 542 metres (1,778 ft), much of Hyderabad is situated on hilly terrain around artificial lakes, including Hussain Sagar—predating the city\'s founding—north of the city centre.Hyderabad was historically known as a pearl and diamond trading centre, and it continues to be known as the City of Pearls.Many of the city\'s traditional bazaars remain open, including Laad Bazaar, Begum Bazaar and Sultan Bazaar. Industrialisation throughout the 20th century attracted major Indian manufacturing, research and financial institutions, including Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited, the National Geophysical Research Institute and the Centre for Cellular and Molecular Biology. Special economic zones dedicated to information technology have encouraged companies from India and around the world to set up operations in Hyderabad.</item>
            <item name="Lucknow">Lucknow is the capital of the Indian state of Uttar Pradesh and is also the administrative headquarters of the eponymous District and Division. It is the largest city in Uttar Pradeshthe eleventh most populous city and the twelfth most populous urban agglomeration of India. In North India, it is the third largest city after Delhi and Jaipur. Lucknow has always been known as a multicultural city that flourished as a North Indian cultural and artistic hub, and the seat of power of Nawabs in the 18th and 19th centuries. It continues to be an important centre of governance administration, education, commerce, aerospace, finance, pharmaceuticals, technology, design, culture, tourism, music and poetry.</item>
            <item name="Chennai">Chennai is the capital of the Indian state of Tamil Nadu. Located on the Coromandel Coast off the Bay of Bengal, it is one of the biggest cultural,economic and educational centres in South India. According to the 2011 Indian census (adjusted for the new limits of Chennai city), it is the fourth-largest city and fourth-most populous urban agglomeration in India. The city together with the adjoining regions constitute the Chennai Metropolitan Area, which isthe 36th-largest urban area by population in the world. Chennai is among the most visited Indian cities by foreign tourists. It was ranked 43rd most visited city in the world for year 2015. The Quality of Living Survey rated Chennai as the safest city in India. Chennai attracts 45 percent of health tourists visiting India, and 30 to 40 percent of domestic health tourists. As such, it is termed \"India\'s health capital\". As a growing metropolitan city ina developing country, Chennai confronts substantial pollution and other logistical and socio-economic problems.</item>
            <item name="Bangalore">Bangalore is the capital of the Indian state of Karnataka. It has a population of about 8.42 million and a metropolitan population of about 8.52 million, making it thethird most populous city and fifth most populous urban agglomeration in India. It is located in southern India on the Deccan Plateau. Its elevation is over 900 m (3,000 ft) above sea level, the highest of India\'s major cities. Bangalore is sometimes referred to as the \"Silicon Valley of India\" (or \"IT capital of India\")because of its role as the nation\'s leading information technology (IT) exporter. Indian technological organisations ISRO, Infosys, Wipro and HAL are headquartered"in the city. A demographically diverse city, Bangalore is the second fastest-growing major metropolis in India. It is home to many educational and research institutions in India,such as Indian Institute of Science (IISc), Indian Institute of Management (Bangalore) (IIMB), National Institute of Fashion Technology, Bangalore, National Institute of Design,Bangalore (NID R&amp;D Campus), National Law School of India University (NLSIU) and National Institute of Mental Health and Neurosciences (NIMHANS).</item>
            <item name="Mumbai">Mumbai is the capital city of the Indian state of Maharashtra. It is the most populous city in India and the ninth most populous agglomeration in the world, with an estimated city population of 18.4 million. Along with the neighbouring regions of the Mumbai Metropolitan Region,it is one of the most populous urban regions in the world and the second most populous metropolitan area in India, with a population of 20.7 million asof 2011. Mumbai lies on the west coast of India and has a deep natural harbour. In 2008, Mumbai was named an alpha world city. It is also the wealthiest city in India, and has the highest GDP of any city in South, West, or Central Asia. Mumbai has the highest number of billionaires and millionaires among allcities in India.</item>
        </string-array>
    <string-array name="delhi">
        <item name="Tuglaqabaad fort">Tughlaqabad Fort is a ruined fort in Delhi, stretching over 6 km, built by Ghiyas-ud-din Tughlaq, the founder of Tughlaq dynasty, of the Delhi Sultanate of India in 1321, as he established the third historic city of Delhi, which was later abandoned in 1327. It lends its name to the nearby Tughlaqabad residential-commercial area as well as the Tughlaqabad Institutional Area.</item>
        <item name="Humayun\'s Tomb">Humayun\'s tomb is the tomb of the Mughal Emperor Humayun in Delhi, India. The tomb was commissioned by Humayun\'s first wife and chief consort, Empress Bega Begum, in 1569-70, and designed by Mirak Mirza Ghiyas, a Persian architect chosen by her.</item>
        <item name="Safdarjung\'s Tomb">Safdarjung\'s Tomb is a sandstone and marble mausoleum in New Delhi, India. It was built in 1754 in the late Mughal Empire style for the statesman Safdarjung. The monument has an ambiance of spaciousness and an imposing presence with its domed and arched red brown and white coloured structures. Safdarjung was made prime minister of the Mughal Empire (Wazir ul-Mamlak-i-Hindustan) when Ahmad Shah Bahadur ascended the throne in 1748.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="lucknow">
        <item name="Bara Imambara">Bara Imambara is an imambara complex in Lucknow, India, built by Asaf-ud-Daula, Nawab of Awadh, in 1784. It is also called the Asafi Imambara. Bara means big, and an imambara is a shrine built by Shia Muslims for the purpose of Azadari.</item>
        <item name="Chhota Imambara">Chota Imambara, also known as Imambara Hussainabad Mubarak is an imposing monument located in the city of Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India.</item>
        <item name="Satkhanda">The word \‘Satkhanda\’ means Seven-Storeyed. Initially, this building was intended to comprise seven storeys but it’s construction work was later abandoned and thus, only 4 level of it could be completed. Incomplete but nevertheless splendour of heritage architecture, Satkhnada, a red-brick watch-tower, constructed by King Mohammed Ali Shah, is situated near the Chota Imambara.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bombay">
        <item name="Gateway Of India">The Gateway of India is an arch monument built during the 20th century in Bombay, India. The monument was erected to commemorate the landing of King George V and Queen Mary at Apollo Bunder on their visit India in 1911.</item>
        <item name="Haji Ali Dargah">The Haji Ali Dargah is a mosque and dargah located on an islet off the coast of Worli in the southern part of Mumbai. Near the heart of the city proper, the dargah is one of the most recognisable landmarks of Mumbai.</item>
        <item name="Shree Siddhivinayak Ganapati Mandir">The Shree Siddhivinayak Ganapati Mandir is a Hindu temple dedicated to Lord Shri Ganesh. It is located in Prabhadevi, Mumbai, Maharashtra.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bangalore">
        <item name="ISKCON Temple">Sri Radha Krishna Temple has deities of Radha and Krishna located at Rajajinagar, in North Bangalore, Karnataka, India. It is one of the largest ISKCON temples in the world.</item>
        <item name="Lal Bagh">Lalbagh or Lalbagh Botanical Gardens, meaning The Red Garden in English, is a well known botanical garden in southern Bengaluru, India.</item>
        <item name="Vidhana Soudha">The Vidhana Soudha located in Bengaluru, is the seat of the state legislature of Karnataka. It is an imposing building, constructed in a style sometimes described as Mysore Neo-Dravidian</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hyderabad">
        <item name="CharMinar">The Charminar, constructed in 1591, is a monument and mosque located in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The landmark has become a global icon of Hyderabad, listed among the most recognized structures of India.</item>
        <item name="Golkonda">Golkonda, also known as Golconda, Gol konda, or Golla konda, is a citadel and fort in Southern India and was the capital of the medieval sultanate of the Qutb Shahi dynasty, is situated 11 kilometres west of Hyderabad.</item>
        <item name="Hussain Sagar">Hussain Sagar is a heart shaped lake in Hyderabad built by Ibrahim Quli Qutub Shah in 1563, during the rule of Ibrahim Quli Qutub Shah. It is spread across an area of 5.7 square kilometers and is fed by River Musi.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="chennai">
        <item name="The Government Museum">The Government Museum or Madras Museum is a museum of human history and culture located in the neighbourhood of Egmore in Chennai, India. Started in 1851, it is the second oldest museum in India after the Indian Museum in Kolkata.</item>
        <item name="Kapaleeshwarar Temple">Kapaleeshwarar Temple, Mylapore, Chennai is a temple of Shiva located in Mylapore, Chennai in the Indian state of Tamil Nadu. The form of Shiva\'s consort Parvati worshipped at this temple is called Karpagambal is from Tamil.</item>
        <item name="St. Thomas Mount">St. Thomas Mount is a small hillock located in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India, near the neighbourhood of Guindy and very close to Chennai International Airport.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="kolkata">
        <item name="Eden Gardens">Eden Gardens is a cricket ground in Kolkata, India established in 1864. It is the home venue of the Bengal cricket team and the Kolkata Knight Riders in the IPL, and is also a venue for Test, ODI and T20I matches.</item>
        <item name="Howrah Bridge">Howrah Bridge is a bridge with a suspended span over the Hooghly River in West Bengal, India. Commissioned in 1943,the bridge was originally named the New Howrah Bridge, because it replaced a pontoon bridge at the same location linking the two cities of Howrah and Kolkata (Calcutta).</item>
        <item name="The Victoria Memorial">The Victoria Memorial is a large marble building in Kolkata, West Bengal, India, which was built between 1906 and 1921.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ahmedabad">
        <item name="Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel National Memorial">The Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel National Memorial is a museum and exhibition centre dedicated to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel at Moti Shahi Mahal, located in Shahibaug, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, near Civil Hospital, Ahmedabad.</item>
        <item name="Sabarmati Ashram">Sabarmati Ashram is located in the Sabarmati suburb of Ahmedabad, Gujarat, adjoining the Ashram Road, on the banks of the River Sabarmati, four miles from the town hall.</item>
        <item name="Sidi Bashir Mosque">Sidi Bashir Mosque was located in the city of Ahmedabad, Gujarat. Due to its unique construction, the minarates of mosque are also called Jhulta Minar or Shaking Minarets.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>

